RYAN HANRAHAN

California City, CA 93505 ryanhammerdick@gmail.com 4422020595

My name is Ryan Hanrahan, and I live in California City, CA. i graduated from California City High School. diploma obtained August 2007 to July 2011. i started working the day after graduation as: Laborer Canyon, CA March 2018 to January 2020 Restoration Laborer. Ran heavy equipment and restored illegal trails made by off roaders. Production Powder Coat Sprayer. Incotec... I powder coated/sprayed aerospace nuts and bolts to a specific size or demension. Sandwich Artist/ Cashier Subway - California City, CA February 2011 to March 2013 Made sandwiches. I understand these may not be tech jobs but I believe by including my work experience in my cover letter will show not only the diversity in job types and job environments iv'e been in but also the adversity and the ability to learn new things and apply what ive learned quickly. My senior year of high school i took and passed a college beginner HTML/CSS class that also taught us javaScript, JQERY and the DOM it was for early college credits. It is for certain that im in the beginning stages of my coding career but Im a diligent worker and im sincerely eager learn soak up all I can all the time so I believe that im at a stage where I could be working in an industry that I can actually say I enjoy. I've been coding on and off since then but recently these past two years iv'e delved into frontend web developement and making responsive sites and dynamic landing pages, my most recent endeavor was Skillcrush's frontend web development course, I gained a lot out of it like using git command line. Other than that I've mainly self-taught from books ive ordered online, and some of the free boot sites online. My wordpress sites: https://localhost8888phpmyadmindbstructurephpserver1d.wordpress.com https://soniaskitchen393139666.wordpress.com portfolio link: file:///Users/owner/Library/Mobile%20Documents/com~apple~CloudDocs/Downloads/portfolioo/ Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Front End Web Developer/freelance content wiriter

Upwork/Self-Employed - California City, CA

August 2020 to Present

I do every thing you need done on the frontend when it comes to web development and I also have done a couple of content SEO writing jobs including a 1200 word sample article for wikimotive.

Laborer

Imc realstate - Canyon, CA March 2018 to January 2020

Ran heavy equipment and restored illegal trails made by off roaders

Production powder coat sprayer

Incotec inc - Mojave, CA March 2013 to January 2016 I powder coated/sprayed aerospace nuts and bolts to a specific size or demension.

Sandwich Artist/Cashier

Subway - California City, CA February 2011 to March 2013

Made sandwiches.

Restoration Laborer

EDUCATION

High school or equivalent

California City High School - California City, CA August 2007 to July 2011

SKILLS

- Construction Laborer
- General Labor
- General Laborer
- Landscaping
- Roofing
- Factory
- Forklift
- Excavator operator
- Assembly Line Mechanical Skills: Aptitude
- Proficient January 2020 Understanding and applying mechanical concepts and processes. Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share
- assignment/wyc8wnngcrz-bjfz Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.
- · Warehouse Associate
- Assembly Line
- React (Less than 1 year)
- · CSS (3 years)
- Front-End Development (1 year)
- JavaScript (1 year)
- Web Development (2 years)
- Node.js (Less than 1 year)
- MySQL (1 year)
- User Interface (UI)
- HTML5 (3 years)
- WordPress (1 year)
- · Graphic Design (1 year)
- Logo Design (1 year)
- SEO content writing (2 years)

ASSESSMENTS

Vehicle Maintenance — Familiar

January 2020

Knowledge of vehicles, vehicle maintenance, and repairs.

Full results: Familiar

Customer Focus & Orientation — Familiar

January 2020

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity.

Full results: Familiar

Attention to Detail — Proficient

January 2020

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting information.

Full results: Proficient

Mechanical Knowledge — Familiar

January 2020

Understanding and applying mechanical concepts and processes.

Full results: Familiar

Basic Maintenance and Repair — Proficient

January 2020

Performing basic repairs and maintenance for apartment complexes, office buildings, and other facilities.

Full results: Proficient

Mechanical Skills: Monitoring — Familiar

January 2020

Monitoring machine indicators to determine appropriate functioning.

Full results: Familiar

Delivery Driver — Proficient

January 2020

Interpreting instructions, reading maps, and solving problems.

Full results: Proficient

Mechanical Skills: Aptitude — Proficient

January 2020

Understanding and applying mechanical concepts and processes.

Full results: Proficient

Construction Safety — Proficient

January 2020

Using safe practices while on a construction site.

Full results: Proficient

Retail Customer Service — Proficient

February 2020

Comprehending and responding to retail customer needs.

Full results: Proficient

${\bf Programming\ Fundamentals\ --\ Completed}$

August 2020

Designed by engineering managers and real-world employers, this test gives you hard data points to evaluate technical competency.

Full results: Completed

Search Engine Optimization — Familiar

August 2020

Interpreting online website performance metrics and understanding search engine optimization tactics.

Full results: Familiar

Graphic Design — Completed

August 2020

Using graphic design techniques and producing visual media to communicate concepts.

Full results: Completed

Work Style: Reliability — Completed

February 2020

Tendency to be dependable and come to work.

Full results: Completed

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.